(ナルト)多重影分身の術！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(角都)影分身を３体…。
Three Shadow Clones...?
(いの)何なの？ あれ…。
What's that?!
(チョウジ)すごい… 高音…
な… なんてチャクラだ…。
What a...high pitched...Chakra!
アイツら 何を…。
What...are they?
What is that Jutsu?!
《なんだ？ あの術は…。
あれをくらったら やばい…。
絶対に ダメだ…》
If I get hit with that...then I'm...
definitely doomed.
風遁 螺旋手裏剣！
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
これで決めるってばよ！
This is the end!
おう！
- Yes!
ボクも加勢する！
(ヤマト)ダメだ。
I'll back him up, too!
No!
(ヤマト)ナルトに近づくな。
巻き添えをくうよ。
Don't get close to Naruto,
or you'll also get caught!
これが 人柱力の九尾の力か。
So this is the power of
the Nine-Tailed Fox's Jinchuriki...
バケモノらしい術だ。
A fitting Jutsu for a monster.
なに!?
What?!
おら!!
(角都)しまっ…。
Damn--!
え…？
What...?
なに？ 勝ったの…？
What? Did he win?
失敗だ…。
Failed...
Wind Style:
Rasen Shuriken
うっ… うわっ！
(カカシ)さすがは 意外性の忍者だ。
やってくれる… ヤマト！
Always the unpredictable Ninja.
He did it again...
- Yamato!
- Right!
はい！
心臓を いただく。
I'll take your heart.
Damn!
はっ！
クソッ！
Damn it!
はぁ… かっこつけるだけ
つけといて。
Gee... Acting really tough...
ナルトらしいっつったら
ナルトらしいけど。
That is so Naruto...
螺旋手裏剣とかいうから
ピューッて飛ばすのかと思ったら➡
Since it was called Rasen Shuriken
or whatever,
I thought you'd let it fly...
走ってぶつけないとダメなの？
Do you have to actually run and punch?
何だよ！ 当たればすげえんだぞ！
Hey! When it hits the target,
it causes some serious damage!
う～ん。
(ヤマト)螺旋手裏剣といっても➡
It's called the Rasen Shuriken, but...
ゼロ距離で
相手にぶつけないとダメなんです。
you must hit at point-blank range.
だから影分身で陽動をかけるのが
この術の基本だったんですが。
That's why this Jutsu relies on
Shadow Clones as a diversion.
(カカシ)まだ新術の
発動持続時間が短すぎるな。
The duration of this
new Jutsu is too short.
もって数秒か…。
(ヤマト)そんなところです。
It only lasted a couple seconds.
Exactly.
それじゃ 当てられないよ。
You'll never hit the target with that.
あんなヤツ相手に。
Not against someone like him.
That Nine-Tailed kid's Jutsu...
《角都 : 九尾のガキのあの術。
威力は相当ありそうだが➡
It seemed very powerful...
近づかなければ大丈夫だな。
but I'll be safe as long
as I keep my distance.
接近戦を避け 術を持つオリジナルに
常に注意をはらっていれば➡
As long as I avoid close-range combat
and watch the one using that Jutsu,
さほど怖くはない》
I have nothing to fear.
もう一度
オレにやらせてくれってばよ。
Please let me try one more time.
新術で決めてやる！
I'll finish him with my new Jutsu.
You're against that "Akatsuki"!
相手は暁だよ。 また同じことを
やっても かわされるだけよ。
If you do the same thing,
he'll just dodge it again!
一度陽動がバレたらもう ダメだよ。
If he detects our diversion,
we're done for.
みんなで やろう。
Let's fight him together...
確かにな。
この状況 今は５対１だ。
That's true...
Our current situation,
it's five against one.
危ない橋を渡る必要もない。
There's no need to take chances.
《さて どう来る？》
So...what's their next move?
カカシ先生。
Kakashi Sensei...
修業中に
オレに言ったこと覚えてるか？
Do you remember what
you told me when I was training?
うん？
四代目火影を超える
忍は お前しかいないって。
You said you believe
I'm the only Shinobi
そう信じてるって。
who can surpass the Fourth Hokage.
ナルト？
Naruto...
確かに チームワークは大事だ。
I know teamwork is important.
危ない橋ってこともわかってる。
I also know that
this is a very risky path.
でも今オレは その危ない橋を
１人で渡りたいんだってばよ。
Even so, I want to take this risk alone.
向こうへたどり着けなきゃ
オレはいつまでたってもガキのままだ。
If I can't beat this,
I'll never be able to grow up.
だから…。
So please...
だから その橋を
はずすようなことはしないでくれ。
Please...
don't take this path away from me.
フッ…。
ヤマト お前は どうだ？
えぇ。
Yamato, what do you think?
Yeah...
だって まだ見てないですよね。
You haven't even seen it yet,
after all.
以前のナルトとは 別人だってところ。
You haven't seen how
he's a completely different Naruto now.
(カカシ)決まりだな。
Then it's settled...
(サクラ)シカマル…。
Shikamaru...
パックン 今のは!?
(パックン)近いぞ！
Pakkun! What was that?!
They're close!
(飛段)ハハ… ヒャーッハッハ！
なんてザマだ これ…。
This is a sorry state...
オレを こんなにしやがって…！
How dare you do this to me?!
(飛段)ハッハッハッハ…！
テメエには 必ず
ジャシン様のバチが当たる！
Lord Jashin will punish you for this!
ジャシン教により
大いなる裁きが お前に～っ！
A greater judgment will be
handed down by Jashin himself!
(シカマル)そんなもん
怖かねえんだよ。
That doesn't scare me.
We believe in different things.
オレとお前じゃ
信じてるもんが違う。
オレが信じてるのは 火の意志だ。
I believe in the Will of Fire.
But your god is not that stupid Jashin
or anything.
(シカマル)だが テメエの神は➡
その くだらねえ
ジャシン様でもなんでもねえ➡
今は… このオレだ。
Now...I will hand down judgment...
オレが 裁きを下す。
テメエ…！
You jerk...!
さっき 言ったよなぁ！
I told you, judgment will be handed down
to you by Lord Jashin!
テメエには ジャシン教により
裁きが下るってよぉ！
なぁ！ ガハハハハ！
その裁きを下すのは オレだ！
And I will carry out that judgment!
I only need teeth to take care of you!
テメエなんて 歯だけで十分だ!!
よく噛んで バラバラにしてやるぜ！
I'll chew you up into little pieces!
(パックン)見つけたぞ！
We found you!
(シカマル)増援か…
けど ひと足遅かったな。
Reinforcements, huh?
But you were just a bit too late...
な… なに？ シカマル！
Wh-What?!
Shikamaru...
You defeated an Akatsuki by yourself?
アンタ １人で暁やっちゃったの!?
(サイ)この人 案外すごいんですね。
You're more impressive than I thought.
(シカマル)まぁな…。
I guess...
今回ばかりは 何がなんでも
ってヤツだったんでな。
I just had to do this myself,
no matter what.
そうよね…。
That's right...
向こうは どうなってる？
What's happening with the others?
(サクラ)私たちは
すぐ こっちへ向かったから…。
We came straight here, so...
(サイ)急いで 合流しよう。
Let's rejoin them quickly.
うわ… うぅ！
あ！ シカマル！
Shikamaru!
ねぇ 大丈夫？ 今 治療を…。
Hey, are you okay?
I'll heal you right now.
…このくらい 問題ねえ。
でも…。
This is no big deal...
But...!
うぅ…。
もう 仲間が傷つくような
面倒くせぇことは➡
I don't like troublesome things
that hurt my friends.
ごめんだからな。
…あ。
(シカマル)急ごう。
うん。
Let's hurry.
Yeah.
《みんな 無事でいて…》
Guys, please be okay...
いけ ナルト。
オッス！
Go, Naruto.
Right!
《また あのガキでくるか。
That kid's going to attack again...?
念のため 遠距離タイプに
かえたほうがいいな》
Just to be safe, I should switch
to a long-range attack style.
あっ…。
うわ…。
体型をかえただけじゃなく
チャクラも かなり練りこんでる…。
He didn't just change
the shape of his body.
He's built up quite a bit of Chakra.
ナルトの術に対応するためだな。
It's to counter Naruto's Jutsu.
影分身の術。
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
《きたな…》
Here he comes...
できた！
It's ready!
飛んだ！
He flew!
《後ろの陽動の影分身は 無視だ》
I can ignore the diversionary
Shadow Clones behind me.
《狙うは オリジナルただ一人。
I just need to aim for the original.
あの術さえ つぶせば怖くない》
I've nothing to fear if
I can just smash that Jutsu...
ダメだ！ 読まれてる。
No! He's reading him!
《やはり 遠距離攻撃か！》
I knew he'd go with a long-range attack!
ナルト！
Naruto!
よし…。
All right!
《なに!? 影分身だと？》
What?! That was a Shadow Clone?!
Huh?!
《角都 : コイツ…。
He mixed himself in with
the diversionary Clones!
陽動の中にオリジナルを…》
あたり～！
Eat this!
ぐっ…。
(ヤマト)爆風が来るぞ！
The blast is coming!
うわぁ～!!
《攻撃回数がケタはずれだ！
That was an extraordinary amount
of attacks.
写輪眼でも見きれなかった》
I couldn't even count them all
with the Sharingan.
《カカシ : なんて術だ…》
What a Jutsu...
す…。
すごい…。
- Awe...
- Awesome.
Naruto...
《カカシ : ナルト… お前…。
お前 ついに！》
ハァ ハァ… ヘヘッ！
よし！ やったぜ！
みんな 元気かな！
今日 挑戦するのは これ！
くちよせの術？
そう！ 時空間忍術の一種で➡
契約をかわした生きものを
好きなときに呼び出す術だよ。
みんなは まだ 口寄せ動物と
契約をしていないから➡
今回は 印の練習をするよ。
(カカシ)必要な印は…。
あとは 呼び出したい場所に
チャクラを練って 手を突き出す！
焦らず 正確にやるのがポイントだよ。
それじゃ やってみよう！
はい！
亥 戌 酉 申 未！
手を突き出して！ どんっ！
よぅ！
呼ばれて飛び出た パックンじゃ！
術の成功に必要なのは
たゆまぬ努力と 修業！
あのナルトだって➡
はじめから ガマ親分を
呼び出せたわけじゃないからね。
たくさん修業して
この術をものにしろ！
それじゃ バイバ～イ！